nationalgeneral.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - National General Insurance

**Overview of Online Privacy Policy for National General Insurance***

You take online privacy seriously and so does National General Insurance. We are a group of companies committed to protecting the personal information of visitors to our web sites and web pages. This policy is one way of sustaining your trust in our companies, our products and our services.

This Online Privacy Policy applies only to the National General Insurance web sites and web pages from which you directly linked to this policy. This policy applies only to the collection, use and sharing of information you provide online.

Our Online Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from and about you during your visit to our web sites and web pages. Our privacy policy also describes how we use information about you, whom we share it with, and how we protect it.

Our web sites and web pages may contain links to third party sites not controlled by National General Insurance or covered by this Online Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy statement of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.

National General Insurance Customers: Once you become a customer of National General Insurance, and annually thereafter while you remain a customer of National General Insurance, we will provide you a Privacy Notice describing our privacy practices related to the collection and sharing of personal information about our customers, as required by law.

  1. What Personal Information Does National General Insurance Collect Online?
  2. How Do You Use the Personal Information You Collect About Me Online?
  3. Do You Share the Personal Information You Collect About Me Online?
  4. Do You Use Cookies or Other Online Technologies to Collect Information About Me?
  5. How Can I Change or Update the Personal Information You Collected About Me Online?
  6. What Steps Do You Take to Protect Personal Information About Me?
  7. Will You Make Changes to this Privacy Policy?

**1\. What Personal Information Does National General Insurance Collect Online?**

We collect personal information about you from the information you provide to us when you visit our web sites and web pages.

The information will depend on the National General Insurance web site or web page you visit. This information may include:

  * name,

  * address,

  * social security number in whole or in part,

  * telephone number,

  * National General Insurance policy or account number

  * account number at a bank or other financial institution, type of bank account, and the name of the bank or other financial institution,

  * email address,

  * email referral information, and

  * date of birth.

Top  

**2\. How Do You Use the Personal Information You Collect About Me Online?**

We use the personal information we collect online to process your request for services, products or information. For example, if you complete a National General Insurance quote form, we may use the information you provide to develop an accurate quote for you. We may also use the information we collect for analytic purposes, market research or for marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

Top  

**3\. Do You Share the Personal Information You Collect About Me Online?**

We may share some of the information we collect about you to third parties, such as companies performing services on our behalf, to provide the products or services you have requested.

We may share information we collect about you with companies with whom we have formal agreements to offer you financial products and services.

We may also share information about you with non-affiliates for analysis, market research and marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

We may disclose your personal information as otherwise permitted or required by law.

Any company with which we share information about you for the above purposes is contractually required to comply with confidentiality standards. 

Top  

**4\. Do You Use Cookies or Other Online Technologies to Collect Information About Me?**

When you browse or visit one of our web sites, we may store certain information on our computer. This information may be in the form of a small text file called a "cookie" and can help us to tailor our sites to your individual preferences and save you time if you visit the site again. For example, cookies may include the country web page you prefer or your language preference. Where specific programs associated with our web sites require a user ID and password, you have the option of requesting that we save your user ID and password so that you will not have to re-enter that information the next time you access the web site. This is accomplished by the placement of a cookie on your computer.

We may also use cookie technology or other online tracking technologies, like web beacons, to gather information about your visit to our web sites. This information allows us to measure site activity and to improve your experience on our sites and may include the time and length of your visit, the web pages you look at on our sites, the web site you visited just before coming to ours and your internet services provider. If we provide you a link from a National General Insurance site to another site, we may track the fact that you navigated to that other site from ours, and we may track your activity while on that site. This will help us understand which links are helpful to you when you visit our site, and will help us provide you with links that may be of interest to you, when you visit our site again. Our website may also use a website recording service which may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, page scrolling and any text keyed into website forms. Data collected by this service is used to improve our website usability. The information collected is stored and is used for aggregated and statistical reporting, and is not shared with anybody else.

Top  

**5\. How Can I Change or Update the Personal Information You Collected About Me Online?**

If you have questions about information you provided on a National General Insurance web site or web page, call the phone number or select the "Contact National General Insurance" link provided on the specific web page, so that we may assist you.

Top  

**6\. What Steps Do You Take to Protect Personal Information About Me?**

We restrict access to the information obtained from our web sites and web pages to our employees, agents and contractors. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect your personal information.

Top  

**7\. Will You Make Changes to this Privacy Policy?**

This policy is effective August 10, 2009. We reserve the right to alter this privacy policy at our discretion. Any change to this policy will be posted on our web sites in a timely manner.

Top
